Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the Vice-President Records 1937-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Ogburn, William F., 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Ogburn, William F., 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Opal, Chester, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Oriental Institute, 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Oriental Institute, 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Ovaltine, 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- P, general, 1937-1938, Parker, Mrs. M Parsons, Keith (Box 45, Folder 32)
- P, general, 1937-1938, Pinkham, Richard A. R. Prentice, Hale Price, Ernest B. Private Schools Association Provines, June Public Administration Clearing House "Public Relations" group meeting Pusey, William A. (Box 45, Folder 33)
- P, general, 1938-1939, Page, A. W. (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Pi, general, 1938-1939, Plunkett, Alice Pontiac Motor Company Postal Telegraph Price, Ernest R. Pulse Purchasing Department Pure Milk Association (Box 45, Folder 35)
- P, general, 1939-1940, Pachman, Dr. Pacific Sound Equipment Co. Pard, I. J. Parker, Leslie M. Patterson, Eleanor Medill Patton, John W. Payson, Laurence O. Pearson, Drew Pennsylvania State College Pennsylvania, University of Pepper, Senator G. W. Perlstein, Harris Pfanstiehl, Cody Phemister, Dallas B. Phillips, A. W. (Box 45, Folder 36)
- P, general, 1939-1940, Pijoan, Joseph Pistey, R. C. Pollak, Mrs. R. K. Pollak, Mr. R. K. Pontius, Clarence Prentice, Pierre Prickett, Charles F. Prince, M. Princeton Listening Center Pritchard, Stuart Professorial Staff Public Opinion Quarterly Pulse (Box 45, Folder 37)
- P, general, 1940-1941, Paley, William Palmer, A. W. Palmer, Philip Paraffine Company Parsons, Geoffrey Patterson, John C. Paulison, Walter Payne, George Pearce, Charles A. Perkins, John S. Philantair presentation Philco Radio and Television Corporation Philips Phillips, Frank Pick, Frieda Pontius, Clarence Powell, D. N. Power, Leonard Pratt, Alice Price, Ernest B. Pride, Armistead Printing Products Corporation Probst, George Pryor, Arthur Public Opinion Quarterly Pulse (Box 45, Folder 38)
- P, general, 1941-1942, Page, A. W. Palyi, Melchior Parker, R. A. Parran, Thomas Parsons, J. G. Patterson, Ellmore Patterson, Joseph Patterson, N. S. Paulison, Walter Penn, William, College Perkins, Milo Perlee, J. B. Pfanstiehl, Cody Pflaum, Irving Phillips, B. O. Phillips, W. B. Pierce, Russell Poole, William Porter, Mrs. Rachel Potter, Roger D. Potter, Gager Prentis, H. W., Jr. Prescott, Daniel A. Price, Byron Public Administration Clearing House Public Affairs Committee Public Relations Investigation Service Publications Section, Division of Information (Box 45, Folder 39)
- P, general, 1942-1943, Pan-American Airways System Papenek, Jan (E. Benes) Parker, Everett Parker, Mary Patterson, W. A. Pfanstiehl, Cody Pflaum, Irving Planned Parenthood of America, Inc. P. M. Private Maroon Progressive Education Association Puckey, Frank Pulliam, Roscoe (Box 45, Folder 40)
- P, general, 1943-1944, Patterson, W. A. Perry, H. C. Pettijohn, F. J. Pflaum, Irving Pollak, Robert Poynter, Nels Pratt, Wallace E. Pulling, Arthur C. (Box 45, Folder 41)
- P, general, 1944-1945, Paine, Ralph D. Palmer, R. W. Pares, Sir Bernard Patton, James Paul, Randolph Pearson, Mowbray Peck, William N. Perkins, Milo Peterson, A. T. Peterson, Elmer Peyton, J. N. Phillips, Charles F. Pitsch, Marion Polin, Martin Pollak, Robert Power, Leonard Prichard, Edward F. Pringle, Henry F. Pritchett, C. H. Pulliam, E. C. Pullman, Kennety (Box 45, Folder 42)
- P, general, 1945-1946, Paepcke, Walter Palmer, Walter L. Parker, Everett C. Peurifoy, John E. Potter, Alden A. Preston, Marguerite Prichard, Edward F. Pulliam, Donald (Box 45, Folder 43)
- Palmer, Dr. Walter L, 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Palyi, Melchior, 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Palyi, Melchior, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Palyi, Melchior, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Patterson, Ellmore, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Personnel, movies, 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Personnel, publicity, 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Personnel, radio, 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Personnel, university, 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Personnel, publicity, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Personnel, radio director, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Personnel, correspondence with Sherman Dryer, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Personnel, recommendations for Sherman Dryer, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Personnel, university, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Personnel, Radio Office, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Personnel, university, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Personnel, Radio Office, 1941-1942 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Personnel, Radio Office, George Probst, 1941-1942 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Peters, H. W., Tax Commission, 1941-1942 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Peters, H. W., 1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Pfanstiehl, Cody, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Pflaum, Irving, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Platt, Robert S., 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Plimpton, N. C., 1937-1938 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Porter, Rachel, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Porter, Rachel, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- President's Office Expense Special Budget, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Press, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Press, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Press, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Press, 1941-1942 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Press, 1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Press, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Press Relations, Harry Barnard, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Press Relations, budget, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Press Relations, Chester Opal, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 36)
- Price, Ernest B., 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- Price, Ernest B., 1941-1942 (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Public Policy pamphlets, 1937-1938, Sloan, Harold Gideonse, Harry Garett, Paul Rating by Departments, Association of American Colleges, by R. M. Hughes, 1924 History of Department of Economics Bean, Donald Commission on Consumer Finance, Cover and Mitchell (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Public Relations budget, Public Relations budget 1937-1938 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Public Relations budget, Pro Arts Concerts, 1937-1938 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Public Relations budget, Public Relations ledger sheets, 1937-1938 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Public Relations budget, Radio Office, Chapel broadcasts, 1937-1938 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Public Relations budget, donor relations, 1938-1939 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Public Relations budget, supplementary radio expense, 1938-1939 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Public Relations budget, 1938-1939 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Public Relations budget, 1939-1940 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Public Relations budget, 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Public Relations budget, suggested revisions, 1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Public Relations budget, Sixth Corps area accounts, 1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Public Relations budget, Time reports appointments, 1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Public Relations budget, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Q, general, 1937-1938, Quadrangle Club (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Q, general, 1938-1939, Quandrangle club Quantrell, Ernest (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Q, general, 1939-1940, Quandrangle Club Quantrell, Ernest (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Q, general, 1941-1942, Quantrell, Ernest Quinn, James B. (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Q, general, 1944-1945, Quadrangle Club Quantrell, Ernest Quebedeaux W. C. Quibley, Harold (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Q, general, 1945-1946, Quantrell, Ernest (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Quadrangle Club, 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Quadrangle Club, 1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Quadrangle Club, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Quadrangle Club, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Quadrangle Club, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Quantrell, Ernest, 1937-1938 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Quantrell, Ernest, 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Quantrell, Ernest, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Quantrell, Ernest, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Quintana, Carlos, 1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- R, general, 1937-1938, Raney, M. Lewellyn Raney, Alma (Mrs. M. L.) Ratner, Herbert Reavis, William C. Redfield, Robert Reid, Mrs. Ogden Reynolds, Theiza G. Rippy, J. Fred (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Ro, general, 1937-1938, Robinson, Milton E. Rogers, Lindsay Rohde, Ruth Bryon Ross, Lanny Russell, John Ryerson, Edward L. (Box 48, Folder 2)
- R, general, 1938-1939, Radio Guide Raney, M. L. Reid, Helen Rogers (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Ro, general, 1938-1939, Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, Laurance Rockefeller, Nelson Rockefeller, Foundation Rosenwald, Julius, Fund Russell, John D. Ryerson, Edward L. (Box 48, Folder 4)
- R, general, 1939-1940, Randall, William N. Raney, M. L. Rashevsky, N. Raskin, Kenneth Ratner, Mrs. Victor Registrar Reid, Helen Rogers Reynolds, J. H. Reynolds, Wilfred Rice, W. R. Richards, Thomas Richardson, W. R. Riley, Elizabeth M. (Box 48, Folder 5)
- R, general, 1939-1940, Rockefeller, David Rockefeller Foundation Rotarian Rothschild Ruml, B. Ruml, Wentzle, III Rush Medical College Ryerson, Mrs. Edward L. Ryerson, Edward L. (Box 48, Folder 6)
- R, general, 1940-1941, Rahill, Mrs. Gerald Ramsdell, Sayre M. Randall, William Raney, M. L. Rankin, Thomas Raskin, S. Kenneth Rawson, Mrs. Frederick H. Raymond, James W. Reavis, William Reck, W. E. Reed, Mrs. Kersey Coates Rich, Raymond Richardson, Smith Rippy, J. Fred (Box 48, Folder 7)
- R, general, 1940-1941, Robertson, C. A. Robertson, O. H. Robertson, S. J. Robson, William Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, John D., Jr. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rogers, Hopewell L. Rohde, Ruth Bryan Rosenberg, L. H. Rosenwald, Lessing Rosso, A. R. Rotarian Rothschild, Maurice L. Rothschild, Melville Ruhm, Herman Ruml, B. Ruml, Wentzle, III Rusch, Hugh L. Russell, Alice Russell, John Dale Ryerson, Edward L. (Box 48, Folder 8)
- R, general, 1941-1942, Radio Productions, Inc. Radio Retailing Today Rainey, Homer P. Rand, Frank L. Randall, William Raney, M. L. Read, W. T. Reed, Philip D. Reeves, Floyd Reilly, William J. Remington, Horace W. Renegar, Horace Rentschler, Gordon Resch, F. A. Richardson, H. Smith Rippy, J. Fred Rix, Carl B. (Box 48, Folder 9)
- R, general, 1941-1942, Robertson, Elizabeth Robertson, Scott Robinson, Irwin Rockefeller, John D., Jr. Roper, Elmo Rose, William C. Rosenberg, Anna Rosenlof, G. W. Rosenwald, Lessing Rotary International Rothschild, Mrs. Melville N. Rubican, Ray Rubins, Pearl C. Rugg, Herbert D. Rural Education Russell, Jack Rutgers University Ryder, F. A. (Box 48, Folder 10)
- R, general, 1942-1943, Raley, James Raney, M. L. Reading, George Reeves, Floyd Reid, Ira Rickenbacker, Edward Rippy, J. Fred (Box 48, Folder 11)
- R, general, 1942-1943, Robertson, Elizabeth Rockefeller, Nelson Roosevelt, Eleanor Rossby, C. G. Ruml, B. Russell, John Ryerson, E. L. (Box 48, Folder 12)
- R, general, 1943-1944, Randall, Clarence Randall, Harris K. Redfield, Robert H. Reid, Helen Reinhold, R. T. Reynolds, Helen Rippy, J. Fred Rix, Carl B. (Box 48, Folder 13)
- R, general, 1943-1944, Rochford, Daniel Rockefeller Foundation Rockefeller, John D., III Rockwell, C. F. Roosevelt, George Rose, Stuart Rossby, Carl G. Rovetta, Charles Rubicam, Raymond Ruml, B. Rydell, Paul Ryerson, Edward L. Ryther, Thomas (Box 48, Folder 14)
- R, general, 1944-1945, Randall, Clarence Randall, Harris K. Randall, J. G. Reavis, William C. Reeve, Edward C. Renne, R. R. Reynolds, Stanley Rheinstein, Max Richardson, W. C. Richmond, Earl C. Richmond News Leader Richter, Richard Ricketts, Henry Riefler, Winfield Riley, James J. (Box 48, Folder 15)
- R, general, 1944-1945, Robinson, Hubbell Rochlen, A. M. Roller, William Roosevelt, Franklin D. Roselle, Anne Rosser, Pearl Ruby, Henry Rupple, Louis Russell, Paul Ryan, D. (Box 48, Folder 16)
- R, general, 1945-1946, Randall, Clarence Redfield, Robert Ricketts, Henry T. Riefler Rovensky, Joe (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Radio Talks, First speech, criticisms, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Radio Talks, Answers to requests for reprints, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Radio Talks, Comments on radio talk of November 15, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Radio Talks, First speech, general, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Radio Talks, First speech, lists, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Radio Talks, Second speech, general, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Radio Talks, Second speech, comments and requests, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Radio Talks, Second speech, lists, 1937-1938 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Radio Talks, Third speech, general, 1937-1938 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Radio Talks – Requests for further radio talks, 1937-1938 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Rainey, Homer P., "University of Chicago Address," 27 September 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Randall, Clarence B., 1937-1938 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Randall, Clarence B., 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Randall, Clarence B., 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Randall, Clarence B., 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Randall, Clarence B., 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Randall, Clarence B., 1942-1943 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Reader's Digest, 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Reader's Digest, 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Reader's Digest, 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Reader's Digest, 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Reader's Digest, 1942-1943 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Reader's Digest, 1943-1944 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Reader's Digest, 1944-1945 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Redfield, Robert, 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Redfield, Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Redfield, Robert, 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Redfield, Robert, 1942-1943 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Redfield, Robert, 1943-1944 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Redfield, Robert, 1944-1945 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Reichelderfer, Francis W., 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Reports on Regional Advertising, 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Rippy, J. Fred, Cultural and Commercial Relations Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Robertson, Ruth, 1945-1946 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Rockefeller, David, 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Rockefeller, John D., III, 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Rockefeller, John D., III, 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1937-1938 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Rockefeller, Nelson, 1937-1938 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Rossby, C. G., 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Rubin, Arthur, 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Rubin, Arthur, 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Ruml, Beardsley, 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Russell, Paul S., 1937-1938 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Russell, Paul S., 1938-1939 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Russell, Paul S., 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Russell, Paul S., 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Russell, Paul S., 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Russell, Paul S., 1942-1943 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Russell, Paul S., 1943-1944 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Russell Sage College Personnel, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- S, general, 1937-1938, Saerchinger, Cesar Sarnoff, David Schlesinger, Hermann I. Schlutz, Dr. F. W. Schultz, Henry Schmeckebier, Lawrence Schoenewald, L. C. Scott, Robert L. (Box 50, Folder 17)
- S, general, 1937-1938, Selfridge, Frank Sellers, Mrs. Elizabeth Sherer, Albert (Box 50, Folder 18)
- S, general, 1937-1938, Slight, David Sloan, Alfred P. Slye, Maud Smith, T. V. (Box 50, Folder 19)
- S, general, 1937-1938, Stapleton, William Steere, Lloyd R. Stephan, Robert Stern, J. David Stevens, David B. Stevenson, A. E. Stolz, Leon Svirsky, Leon Swift, Dr. Charles H. (Box 50, Folder 20)
- S, general, 1938-1939, Sague, S. R. St. Auer St. Louis Post-Dispatch Salavay, Ann Salmon, C. L. Sammons, Neil Sarnoff, David Schenk, C. A. Jr. Schiff, Sydney Scott, Albert L. Scott, William E. Selfridge, Frank Seymour, Charles Sharp, Malcolm Shaughnessy, Clark Shubart, Harry (Box 50, Folder 21)
- S, general, 1938-1939, Simons, Henry Slight, Mrs. David Sloan, Alfred P. Smith, Cecil Smith, Leon P. Smith, T. V. (Box 50, Folder 22)
- S, general, 1938-1939, Steere, Lloyd R. Steinbeck, Alden C. Stift, Walter Stolz, Leon Strauss, Helen Student Forum Stutzman, Frances Swift, Dr. Charles H. (Box 50, Folder 23)
- S, general, 1939-1940, St. Cloud, Minnesota St. John's College Sammons, Neil Sanderson, T. H. Saturday Evening Post Saxton, Eugene F. Schaefer, Walter Schiff, Sidney Scholarships Schlutz, F. W. Schmitt, Bernadotte Schnabel, Arthur Schwab, Joseph Science Service Scott, Albert Scott, Orlando Scribner's, Charles, Sons Scipps-Howard Scripps Newspapers (Box 50, Folder 24)
- S, general, 1939-1940, Selman, Ray Senate Shadbolt, Beulah Shannon, T. V. Sharp, Malcolm Shaughnessy, C. D. Sherer, Albert Shields, Harold Shuler, Carl F. Shumaker, E. E. (Box 50, Folder 25)
- S, general, 1939-1940, Simons, Henry Slye, Maud Smith, K G. Smith, Leon P. Smith, Lloyd Smith, T. V. Smith, Wilton L. Snell Social Sciences Space and Time Spencer, Dean William Spitzer, Horton Spivak, L. Sprengling, Martin (Box 50, Folder 26)
- S, general, 1939-1940, Standard Oil Stephan, Robert F. Sterges, Alfred Stern, Alfred W. Stern Brothers Stevens, Riley Stires, Hardwick Stouffer, Samuel Stout, Wesley Strong, William Strosnider, C. M. Strotz, Sidney Struve, Otto Studebaker, J. W. Swift, Charles H. (Box 50, Folder 27)
- S, general, 1940-1941, Sampson, Paul Sanford, Raymond P. Sarnoff, David Saxton, E. Schell, E. H. Schenk, William Schmidt, Eric Schmidt, Bernadotte Schreiber, Frank P. Schuler, Edgar A. Schwab, Joseph Science Scott, Robert L. Scott, Walter Dill Scribner, Gilbert H. Scipps-Howard Newspapers (Box 50, Folder 28)
- S, general, 1940-1941, Selective Services Seton, Marie Shainmark, Eliazar Sharp, Malcolm Shattuck, Abbott Shaw, Arch Sheldon, Mrs. Mary Strong Sheldon, Theodore Sherer, Albert Sherman, Mandel Shumaker, E. E. (Box 50, Folder 29)
- S, general, 1940-1941, Simmons College Smith Family, Northern Trust Co. Smith, A. Calvert Smith, Frank Smith, Herman D. Smith, Ira Smith, Leon P. Snite, Fred Speed, Carleton D., Jr. Spencer, A. K. Spencer, Dean William Spiegel, Modie J., Jr. Spitz, Leo Spofford (Box 50, Folder 30)
- S, general, 1940-1941, Starrett, Roy Stearn, Allen Stein, Milton Stephan, Robert Stern, Alfred W. Stevens, David Stewart, Russell Stock, Frederick Stolz, Leon Stouffer, Samuel Stout, Wesley Straus, Robert Stuart, John Stuart, Mrs. R. Douglas, Jr. Stutzman, Frances Sunny, B. E. Survey Graphic Swann, H. G. Swift & Co. Swift, Phillip (Box 50, Folder 31)
- S, general, 1941-1942, Sage, Robert L. Sandberg, John V. Sandburg, Carl Sarnoff, David Saunders, Alta Schaefer, Walter Schatzmann, Iman E. Scherman, Harry Schlesinger, H. I. Schmidt, Eric Schmidt, Bernadotte Scheiber, Frank Schutze Schwartz, National Attractions Schwartz, S. D. Scott, Albert (Box 50, Folder 32)
- S, general, 1941-1942, Seaton, R. A. Selfridge, Frank Selig, Lester Selvage, James P. Semer, Milton Senate Committee on University Policy Seymour, Charles Shattuck, H. L. Sheldon, Theodore Sherer, Albert Sholl, Harry Shumaker, E. E. (Box 50, Folder 33)
- S, general, 1941-1942, Slesinger, Donald Sloan, Harold Smedley, Agnes Smith, Calvert Smith, Frank Smith, Harold Smith, Herman D. Smith, King William Smith, Leon P. Social Service Administration, School of Soss, Wilma Southwestern Engraving Co. Spencer, Hartnell Spencer, W. H. Spiegel, Modie Sprinkle, John C. Sproul, President Robert G. (Box 50, Folder 34)
- S, general, 1941-1942, Stack Globe Advertising Agency Star Weekly Stratham, Jane Steele, Mrs. O. S. Stein, Sydney Stern, Edgar Stern, J. David Stevens, Alden Stevens, David H. Stevenson, Adlai Stevenson, P. K. Stewart, G. W. Stewart, Myron B. Stewart, Russ Stierham, Eleanor Stolz, Leon Stone, Raleigh Stouffer, E. B. Strawn, Silas Struve, Otto Stuart, John Stuart, R. Douglas Stuart, R. Douglas, Jr. Stubbs, Eric Study of Civilization Stutzman, Frances Survey Associates Sutherland, Eva Sutton, Willis A. Swados, Felice (Box 50, Folder 35)
- S, general, 1942-1943, Salvemini, Gaetano Schafer, MacHenry Schatzmann, Iman Schultz, T. W. Schuster, M. Lincoln Schwab, Joseph J. (Box 51, Folder 1)
- S, general, 1942-1943, Shaw, Arch W. Sherer, A. W. Shubart, Harry (Box 51, Folder 2)
- S, general, 1942-1943, Simons, Henry Slichter, Sumner Smith, Gerald K. Smith, H. D. Smothers, Frank Space and Time (Box 51, Folder 3)
- S, general, 1942-1943, Sterges, Alfred Stevens, David Stevenson, John A. Stromwall, Roma Struve, Otto Stuart, John Stuart, R. Douglas, Jr. Sulzberger, Frank Sutton, Willis (Box 51, Folder 4)
- S, general, 1943-1944, Salter, J. T. Samson, Ruth Saturday Evening Post Schild, Gerhart Schmidt, Emerson P. Schultz, T. W. Science News Letter Scott, Arthur Scott, William (Box 51, Folder 5)
- S, general, 1943-1944, Sensenbrenner, F. J. Sergel, R. L. Seymour, Charles Shakespeare, Monroe Shaw, Arch Shelden, Alger Shen, Li-ren Shubart, Harry Shull, Russell Shumaker, Mrs. E. E. (Box 51, Folder 6)
- S, general, 1943-1944, Simons, Henry Singh, J. J. Smith, Herman D. Smith, S. M. Smith, Winthrop Snyder, C. G. Somers, B. Soule, Frank Southern, Walter A. Spadea, J. V. Spellman, Charles Spencer, W. H. Spivak, Lawrence (Box 51, Folder 7)
- S, general, 1943-1944, Stanton, Frank Steele, Westbrook Steinhoff, William Stellmacher, H. L. Stevens, E. T. Stevenson, John Stock, Dorothy Stoke, Harold Stotes, Amos Struve, Otto Stuart, John Sulzberger, Arthur Sulzberger, Frank Survey Associates (Box 51, Folder 8)
- S, general, 1944-1945, Salisbury, Morse Saunders, Sarah C. Sayler, A. W. Scheuer, S. H. Schinnerer, M. C. Schubart, William E. Schuette, Oswald F. Schultz, Theodore W. Schuman, Frederick Schwartz, E. K. Schwartz, L. S. Schwarz, Max Scoon Scott, John W. Scott, William E. (Box 51, Folder 9)
- S, general, 1944-1945, Selden, William K. Serblin, Michael D. Seyfert, Walter C. Seymour, Charles Shainmark, E. L. Shapley, Harlow Shaunessey, James Shaw, Alejandro Shaw, Arch Shepherd, E. Colston Sherer, Albert Shavlin, Mrs. Thomas Shotwell, James T. Shuster, George N. (Box 51, Folder 10)
- S, general, 1944-1945, Siegfried, Thorwald Siepmann, Charles Siever, Paul Simons, Henry Singh, J. J. Slight, David Smead, E. E. Smith, B. B. Smith, Cecil Smith, Hermon D. Smith, T. V. Smith, Zens Sonne, H. C. Soule, Frank F. Souvaine, Mabel Spencer, W. H. Spink, C. C. Spivak, Lawrence Sprague, A. A. (Box 51, Folder 11)
- S, general, 1944-1945, Stefansson, V. Stephens, G. E. Stettinius, Edward Stevenson, John A. Stigler, George Stone, R. W. Strelow, William R. Stromwall, Roma Strong, R. W. Stuart, John Sturgis, Warren Sutherland, R. H. Swift, Charles Swift, Otis Swing, Raymond Gram (Box 51, Folder 12)
- S, general, 1945-1946, Schultz, T. W. Schwartz, L. S. Scoon, John Scott, Betty Seymour, Charles Sharp, Malcolm Sheridan, Mary Shubart, Harry Singer Smith, T. V. Sou, S. K. Spencer, Dean W. H. Stromwall, Roma Struve, Otto Swift, Harold (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Saerchinger, Cesar, 1938-1939 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Say, St. John, 1944-1945 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Sandburg, Carl, 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Sandburg, Carl, 1942-1943 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Sandburg, Carl, 1943-1944 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Saturday Evening Post articles, Robert Maynard Hutchins, 1937-, 1938 "Why go to College?" "We are Getting No Brighter" "Why Send them to School?" "What Can We Do about It?" (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Schairer, Reinhold, 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Schlutz, Dr. F. W., 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Schwab, Joseph J., "Fight for Education," Atlantic, June 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Scott, Albert L., 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Scott, Albert L., 1942-1943 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Scott, William E., 1941-1942 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Scott, William E., 1942-1943 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Shields, Harold G., 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Shubart, Harry, July-February, 1939-1940 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Shubart, Harry, March-June, 1939-1940 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Shubart, Harry, July-August, 1940-1941 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Shubart, Harry, September-October, 1940-1941 (Box 52, Folder 2)